publicrecordsreviews.com 2019-12-15

# Privacy Policy for Searching Records

## 1\. Introduction

This Privacy Policy describes how the site provides access to the people finder and public records (along with all subdomains, collectively, the "Site"). This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy.

## 2\. Information Collection Practices

#### i. Types of Information Collected

Traffic Data Collected. We may automatically track and collect the following categories of information when you visit our Site: (1) IP addresses; (2) domain servers; (3) types of computers accessing the Site; and (4) types of web browsers used to access the Site (collectively "Traffic Data"). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you but is helpful for marketing purposes or for improving your experience on the Site.

Cookies and web beacons are very small text files that are stored on your computer when you visit certain web pages. The site collects information through cookies and web beacons about your web browsing activities such as the address of the page you are visiting, the address of the referrer page you previously visited, the time you are viewing the page, your browsing environment and your display settings. We use cookies and web beacons on our Site for some of the following purposes:

  * Understand traffic patterns and the number of visitors to the Site and other websites that we partner with;
  * Understand how you use and interact with the Site;
  * Improve the products and services;
  * Optimize your experience on our Site;
  * Provide anonymous individual or aggregate auditing, research, modeling and reporting for our advertisers and other partners (no personally identifiable information about you is shared with our advertisers and other partners as part of these activities);
  * Store your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site;
  * Provide you relevant advertising and content; and
  * Properly manage our Site.

Please note that some cookies may be placed by a third party service provider who performs some of these functions for us. Other companies use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies.

Personal Information Collected. In order for you to access and purchase products that we offer via the Site, we may require you to provide us with certain information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information"). Personal Information may include the following categories of information: (1) Contact Data (such as your name, mailing address, and e-mail address); (2) Financial Data (such as your account or credit card number); and (3) Demographic Data (such as your zip code and age). If you communicate with us by e-mail, post messages to any of our chat groups, bulletin boards, or forums, or otherwise complete online forms, surveys, or contest entries, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information.

#### ii. Uses of Information Collected

We may use some of your Personal Information to send you information about our company or our products or services or to contact you when necessary. We may also share some of your Personal Information with some of our partners who may use it to contact you about goods and services. However, under no circumstances will we share your Financial Data with our partners. We use your Financial Data only to verify your qualifications for certain products or services and to bill you for products and services. We do not use your Financial Data for any other purpose.

#### iii. Sharing of Personal Information.

We share certain categories of information we collect from you in the ways described in this Privacy Policy. We may share certain types of Personal Information with advertisers and other third parties. The other parties with whom we share the information may want to send you information about products or services. We do not share your Financial Data with these third parties. We may share Financial Data with our business partners who assist us by performing core services (such as hosting, billing, fulfillment, or data storage and security) related to our operation of the Site. Those business partners have all agreed to uphold the same standards of security and confidentiality that we have promised to you in this Privacy Policy, and they will only use your data to carry out their specific business obligations

**Interest-Based Ads**

We may also share Traffic Data with advertisers and other third parties who may use it for advertising purposes, including to serve targeted advertising on our behalf on non-affiliated third party sites. Some of those ads may be personalized, meaning that they are intended to be relevant to you based on information we or the online advertising network serving the ad collect about your online activities here and elsewhere over time. For example, anonymous information collected across multiple sites that you visit over time may enable the ad network to predict your preferences and show you ads that are most likely to be of interest to you.

Please note that we do not share any information that identifies you personally with the third party service providers who serve ads on our behalf. To opt out of these types of ads, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative for information about how to opt-out of interest-based advertising by their members. See [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) for general information about the NAI and <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> for the opt-out page. You may also visit <http://www.aboutads.info/consumers/> to learn about online behavioral advertising and how to opt-out from online behavioral ads served by some or all participating companies.

If we or some or all of our assets are acquired by another company, including through a sale in connection with bankruptcy, that company will possess the information collected by us, and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose Personal Information or other data to comply with law or legal requirements, enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements, or protect our rights, property, or safety of our users, or others.

#### iv. Email Marketing.

By accepting this Privacy Policy and submitting your email address via the Site, you are expressly consenting to receive e-mail advertisements from the site, including through any independent contractors, and from third parties concerning offers and advertisements unrelated to the site. To opt-out of receiving promotional email messages from us, please click on the “Unsubscribe” link contained at the bottom of each email.

#### v. Contests, Sweepstakes, Surveys

We may conduct or cosponsors contests, sweepstakes, or other offerings. In such circumstances, the information we obtain from you may be shared with our co-sponsor. Our co-sponsors will have the right to use your information for their own purposes, in accordance with their own policies. If you do not wish for the information we obtain from you to be shared with our co-sponsor, you may decline participation.

## 3\. Confidentiality and Security of Personal Information

#### i. User Ability to Access, Update, and Correct Personal Information

We maintain a procedure in order to help you confirm that your Personal Information remains correct and up-to-date. At any time, you may contact us to update your Personal Information or request that your Personal Information no longer be shared by the site. In the case that your credit card, user name, or password is lost, stolen, or used without permission, promptly contact us to update the Personal Information we have on file for you.

#### ii. Your California Privacy Rights

You may remove your Personal Information from the database. If you remove your information from the database it will no longer be used by the site for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by the site or third parties to send promotional correspondence to you.

#### iii. Security

The information stored on the site’s computer use industry standard security measures (such as a firewall and password protections) in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under the Sites control. Notwithstanding such measures, we cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent its computers from being illegally accessed, and the Personal Information on them stolen or altered.

## 4\. Public Information

The Site contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. In the future, we may also make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and news groups available to you. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information.

## 5\. Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site.
